<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Andrew Walpole Blog</title>
  <subtitle>Long-winded musings about web development, leadership and other top-of-mind ramblings</subtitle>
  <link href="https://andrewwalpole.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://andrewwalpole.com/"/>
  <updated>2022-04-30T19:33:19Z</updated>
  <id>https://andrewwalpole.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Andrew Walpole</name>
    <email>andrew@andrewwalpole.com</email>
  </author>
  
  <entry>
    <title>First</title>
    <link href="https://andrewwalpole.com/blog/first/"/>
    <updated>2022-04-30T19:33:19Z</updated>
    <id>https://andrewwalpole.com/blog/first/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;April 30, 2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;First&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I did it; after two years and three scrapped site designs – and of course I&#39;m not even that stoked on this one – the itch to blog has been growing, so here I&#39;ve settled to make a go at it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site is built with eleventy, with a custom esbuild setup for the small bits of sass and javascript. It&#39;s hosted on Cloudflare Pages, which is a bit of a departure from my usual choice of vercel or netlify, but I&#39;ve been really happy with Cloudflare workers, so I&#39;m giving this a go as well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What can you expect from this blog?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, probably just a decent bit of web-related punditry and maybe a bit of leadership stuff... Really whatever strikes my fancy I guess. My goal is to publish a healthy mix of useful tech-specific things along with my own views on the way the web development industry is moving, with some sprinkling in of random things I like. If that&#39;s your jam, welcome, feel free to like and &lt;a href=&quot;https://andrewwalpole.com/feed.xml&quot;&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More specifically these topics have a high chance of showing up:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web Development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dev Stacks/Architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serverless non-sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading dev teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robust-first computation via living-systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3D printing tips and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>